https://www.contemplation.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Notice:This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.contemplation.com/shop. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing  We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via this website. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you regarding this order and to fulfill your order. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.Security  We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 866.886.0544 or via email: orders@contemplation.com
